Dylan Armstrong

Orlando, FL | (407) 230-1632 | <u>Dylan.Craig.Armstrong@gmail.com</u>

Linked In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/Dylan-Armstrong

Github: https://github.com/DoleTM | Portfolio: https://doletm.github.io/Portfolio/

SUMMARY

Web Developer specializing in creative front-end web pages and fluid back-end functionality. Experience in inventory management implementing Agile practices such as using an online Kanban board, testing in batches and iterating reusability. Ability to create platforms practical for the end user through hands on experience and connecting data. Strong communication skills with a demonstrated history of leading without authority.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.js | MySQL/Postgres | Javascript | JSON | API | JQuery | MongoDB | React | CSS/SASS | HTML | FTP | PHP | Angular | Version Control/Git | MVC | Bootstrap | OOP | Ember.js | Heroku | Materialize | Command Line

PROJECTS

Safely: A website that uses geolocation or zip code that determines if they are safe based on a crime data API. Deployed site: https://soc33.github.io/Safely/ | GitHub Repo: https://github.com/soc33/Safely

Furiends: Social media website designed for pets that allows the user to upload and comment on pictures.

Deployed site: https://agile-gorge-44903.herokuapp.com/ | GitHub Repo: https://github.com/gutierrez88/Furiends

Web-Scrape: Webpage that scrapes articles using cheerio and saves favorites/comments in a database. Deployed site: https://infinite-bastion-71270.herokuapp.com/ | GitHub Repo:

https://github.cpm/DoleTM/Web-Scrape

EXPERIENCE

AdventHealth, Orlando, FL — *Inventory Control PAR Tech* | Jan 2019 - Present

- Responsible for configuring and maintaining the physical hardware in 200+ automated supply rooms across 8 hospitals in the Orlando area.
- ☐ Analyze trends through client side programs to correct issues by using my database knowledge to prevent problems from occurring in real time.
- Implemented a Kanban board to visualize and maintain the flow of overall project completion and daily activities.
- Provide technical training to the support staff that utilizes the automated hardware daily.

Injector Support & Service, Winter Garden, FL — *Shipping Manager* | Feb 2017 - Dec 2018

- Organized a new 10,000 sqft. warehouse facility, containing 3000+ parts and equipment that maximized efficiency for all departments.
- Recognized by CEO for compiling 8 years of scattered data into one streamlined log within a month.
- Created a comprehensive procedure handbook that establishes guidelines, sets the daily goals and sustains my organizational knowledge.
- Improved the return rate of core exchanges by 50% within a year by keeping a good relationship with customers through email and phone calls.

Victory Tailgate, Orlando, FL — *Production Control Supervisor* | Oct 2014 - Jan 2017

- Supervised a dynamic team of 8 employees in the production control department where I instilled my team with essential time and priority management skills.
- Recognized by manager for constantly displaying strong team building, decision making and people management skills.
- Developed new systems to optimize production flow and inventory management.

Lockheed Martin, Ocala, FL — *Electronic Associate* | Aug 2013 - Oct 2014

- ☐ Created new tools to aid the soldering and cable & harness processes used to piece together the 10 various subassemblies on the program.
- Became responsible for all rework (6 to 8 units a week) by being able to swiftly complete while maintaining quality and not disrupting my daily goals.
- Recognized by manager and program engineers for taking the initiative and having a drive for continual learning.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate (Coding Bootcamp): University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL A 24-week intensive program focused on technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, PHP, AJAX, JSON, Express, Handlebars.js & ReactJS.